{
"1" : {"question": "Введите 3 раза @media через пробел", "rightAnswer": "@media @media @media"},
"2" : {"question": "Стиль для < 1200px ", "rightAnswer": "@media (max-width: 1200px) {}"},
"3" : {"question": "Стиль для < 992px", "rightAnswer": "@media (max-width: 992px) {}"},
"4" : {"question": "Стиль для < 768px", "rightAnswer": "@media (max-width: 768px) {}"},
"5" : {"question": "Стиль для < 480px", "rightAnswer": "@media (max-width: 480px) {}"},
"6" : {"question": "Стиль для < 320px", "rightAnswer": "@media (max-width: 320px) {}"},
"7" : {"question": "Стиль для > 320px", "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 320px) {}"},
"8" : {"question": "Стиль для > 480px", "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 480px) {}"},
"9" : {"question": "Стиль для > 768px", "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 768px) {}"},
"10" : {"question": "Стиль для > 992px", "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 992px) {}"},
"11" : {"question": "Стиль для > 1200px",  "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 1200px) {}"},
"12" : {"question": "768px < Стиль для < 992px", "rightAnswer": "@media (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 992px) {}"}
}